wfan.com 2017-12-28

# Privacy Policy

back to top

#### Scope of Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to information, including contact information, collected about you by the CBS Local Services. Please review this Privacy Policy carefully. In addition, please review our [Terms of Use](http://policies.cbslocal.com/terms-of-use/), which governs your use of the CBS Local Services.

back to top

#### Information Collected

**Information you provide directly to CBS Local Services**.

You are not required to provide information about yourself when you visit a CBS Local Service. CBS Local may ask you for different types of information when you register for certain Services, access various content or features, or contact the Services directly, including: 

  * Contact information, such as name, email address, postal address, phone number, facsimile number, and mobile number;
  * User name, password, and password reminder questions and answers;
  * Age and date of birth;
  * Other demographic information, such as gender, job information, and postal code;
  * Public information, including profile information, you provide to the CBS Local Services for publication, such as your user name, comments, likes, interests, status, pictures and the address of your website;
  * Communications preferences, such as which newsletters you would like to receive;
  * Search queries;
  * In limited circumstances, payment and identity verification information, such as credit card number, social security number or comparable national identifiers, and driver's license number where needed for payment, to complete a particular transaction, or to access a particular service (e.g., contests);
  * Contact information about others when you provide information about others or refer a friend to a particular website or service (note: such information is used solely to facilitate the communications requested);
  * Information posted in community discussions and other interactive online features;
  * Correspondence you send to us; and
  * Information collected about you offline (including via facsimile, postal mail, or in person for sweepstakes entrance forms).

**Information we collect automatically on CBS Local Services**.

CBS Local Services may collect certain information automatically, including:

  * Your browser type and operating system; 
  * Your Internet Protocol (IP) address, which is the number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet and that can sometimes be used to derive your general geographic area; 
  * Websites you visited before and after visiting a CBS Local Service; 
  * Web pages and advertisements you view and links you click on within CBS Local Services; 
  * Unique identifiers, including mobile device identification numbers, that can identify the physical location of such devices in accordance with applicable law; 
  * Information collected through cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies;
  * Information about your interactions with audio and video content, such as the type of content listened to (including music applications such as iTunes, Spotify and Last.fm) and content viewed, and information about your interactions with email messages, such as the links clicked on and whether the messages were opened or forwarded; 
  * Upon request, your bandwidth speed and information about the software programs installed on your computer; and
  * Standard server log information. 

**Information we obtain from other sources**

Where permitted by applicable law, we may collect information about you from other sources, including through interactive applications (e.g., mobile devices, third party services, and embedded audio and video players), from co-branded partners and websites (for example, on our Facebook pages), and from commercially available sources (such as data aggregators and public databases). The following are examples of information we may collect from other sources:

  * Name, postal address, and telephone number; 
  * Demographic data, such as age, gender, and income level; 
  * If you access third party services (e.g., Facebook, Google+ or Twitter) through a CBS Local Service, your username and password for those services and other information available about you on those services, as described in our Video Services and Social Networking Policy;
  * Your interests and purchase behavior; 
  * Publicly-observed data, such as activities on blogs, videos, and other online postings; and
  * Other navigation data, such as websites visited and advertisements viewed or clicked on. 

This Privacy Policy does not cover the practices of third parties, including those that may disclose information to CBS Local.

**Combining Information**

Please note that all of the information we collect about you may be combined, including to help us tailor our communications to you and to develop rich online content and services across the CBS Local Services. 

back to top

#### Use of Information

We only use payment and identity verification information, such as credit card numbers, driver's license numbers, social security numbers, or comparable national identifiers as necessary for completing a particular transaction or fulfilling a service (e.g., paid subscriptions or awarding prizes to contest winners) or as otherwise required by law.

We generally use other information we collect about you to:  

  * Fulfill your requests for products, services, and information, including to send you electronic newsletters, authorize a purchase, and complete a transaction that you have requested;
  * Enable you to participate in features such as surveys, polls, sweepstakes and message boards; 
  * Provide you with special offers and promotional materials on behalf of CBS Local Services, companies within our corporate family, and third parties, in accordance with applicable law; 
  * Analyze the use of CBS Local Services and information about visitors to our Services to understand and improve our offerings and, in accordance with our sharing policies, discussed below, to produce anonymous or aggregated data and statistics that might help third parties develop their own products and service offerings; 
  * Customize the content you see when you visit a CBS Local Service; 
  * Develop and provide advertising tailored to your interests, as described in our overview of CBS Local Online Advertising
  * Prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities and otherwise in accordance with the [CBS Local Terms of Use](http://policies.cbslocal.com/terms-of-use/); and
  * For any other purposes disclosed to you at the time we collect your information or pursuant to your consent. 

back to top

#### Disclosure of Information Collected

CBS Local is committed to maintaining your trust and we want you to understand when and with whom we may share information collected about you.

**With Your Consent**

With your consent, we may share your contact information with third party marketing partners. For example, CBS Local Services such as Eventful offer updates about local events if you allow your information to be shared with third-parties so that they may contact you by email, postal mail. telephone or other common communications methods about their events, products or services. 

**Authorized Third Party Service Providers**

We share your contact information with third party vendors who help us with specialized services, including customer support, email and text message deployment, business analytics, marketing, suppression list management, and data processing. These third parties are allowed to use your contact information to help us provide our services and not for any other purpose. Also, authorized third party service providers may collect non-contact information about your visits to our Services with cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies that may be used to deliver advertisements tailored to your interests. For more information, visit our overview on cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies (including Do Not Track).

**Sweepstakes, Contests, or Promotions**

When you choose to enter a sweepstakes, contest, or other promotion, and in accordance with the terms and conditions of the promotions, your information may be disclosed to our sponsors and to third parties who help administer the promotion, including in connection with winner selection prize fulfillment and aggregated data analysis. Your information also may be disclosed as required by law, such as on a winners list. Further, by entering a promotion, you are agreeing to the official rules that govern that promotion, including allowing our sponsors to use your name, voice, and likeness in advertising and marketing associated with the promotion in accordance with applicable law. All terms applicable to the particular promotion will be made available to you at the time you enter the promotion.

**Co-Branded Partners**

Co-Branded Partners are third parties with whom a CBS Local Service may offer jointly a service or feature. You will be able to tell when you are accessing a service or feature offered by a Co-Branded Partner, because the Co-Branded Partner's name will be featured prominently. You may be asked to provide information about yourself to register for a service offered by a Co-Branded Partner. By doing so, you may be providing your information to both us and the Co-Branded Partner, or we may share your information with the Co-Branded Partner. Please note that the Co-Branded Partner's privacy policy may also apply to its use of your information.

**CBS Local Services and Other CBS Businesses**

CBS Local and other business units of CBS Corporation, our parent company, continue to expand their online presence in order to offer users rich and deep interactive experiences. Where permitted by law, we may share information we collect about you within the family of CBS Local businesses, with [CBS Corporation](http://www.cbscorporation.com/), and with other [CBS-affiliated companies](http://www.cbscorporation.com/portfolio.php), so that we can provide you with information about products and services that might interest you.

**Business Transfers**

We may share your information in connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of a CBS television station participating in the CBS Local Services, a merger, consolidation, asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy. 

**Legal Requirements**

We may disclose information about our users, including contact information, to respond to subpoenas, court orders, legal process, and other law enforcement measures, and to comply with other legal obligations, such as FCC requirements.

**Protect CBS Local Services and Users**

We may disclose information to protect and defend the legal rights, interests, and safety of CBS Local Services, other CBS companies, and their employees, agents, and contractors (including enforcing our agreements); to protect the safety and security of users of the Services and members of the public; and as otherwise disclosed in the [CBS Local Terms of Use](http://policies.cbslocal.com/terms-of-use/).

Please note that we may share information with advertisers as described in our overview of CBS Local Online Advertising.

In addition, information collected about your interactions with audio and video content may be shared with third parties, including third party social networking services such as Facebook, and video measurement and subscription services such as Nielsen, as described in our overview of video services and social networking.

Finally, we also may share aggregated or anonymized information with third parties to help us develop content and services we hope will interest you or to help these third parties develop their own product and service offerings, including targeted marketing, as described in our overview of third party online advertising.

back to top

#### Your Choices

You can choose to enjoy content and features on CBS Local Services without providing us directly with any information about you; however, as described above, some information may be collected automatically or be requested so that you can take advantage of certain features and services offered on CBS Local Services.

You can opt out of receiving commercial email or text messages from a particular CBS Local Service or other service by following the instructions contained in any such message or by [contacting us](mailto:localcontactus@cbs.com?Subject=Contact%20Us) directly. Please note that even if you unsubscribe to commercial messages, we may still need to send you communications relating to your use of the CBS Local Services, such as service announcements.

You have choices about whether cookies and other similar technologies are placed on your computer or mobile device. For more information, visit our overview on cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies (including Do Not Track).

Finally, you also have choices about the collection and use of your information by third parties to display relevant advertisements, as described in the section on Third Party Online Advertising.

back to top

#### Access

If you choose to share contact information with us, you may have the opportunity to update that information on a CBS Local Service. You also may update or amend your information by [contacting us](mailto:localcontactus@cbs.com). If you ask us to shut down your account or delete your information, we will disable your account within a reasonable period of time. Please note that we may need to retain some information about you in order to satisfy our legal and security obligations. For example, some of your information may remain in backup storage even if you ask us to delete it. In some cases, you may be entitled under local laws to access or object to the processing of information that we hold relating to you.

back to top

#### Protection of Information

We are committed to protecting your information. We have adopted commercially reasonable technical, administrative, and physical procedures to help protect your information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access and alteration. Please note that no data transmission or storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We want you to feel confident using CBS Local Services, but we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. Please refer to the [U.S. Federal Trade Commission's website](http://ftc.gov/bcp/menus/consumer/data/idt.shtm) for information on how to protect yourself from identity theft.

back to top

#### Transfer of Data Internationally

CBS Local is headquartered in the United States and has affiliates and partners in other countries. Please be aware that information you provide to us or that we obtain as a result of your use of the CBS Local Services may be collected in your country and subsequently transferred to the United States or another country in accordance with applicable law. The privacy and data protection laws in the country to which your information is transferred may not be equivalent to such laws in your country of residence. By using and participating in any CBS Local Services or providing us with your information, you consent to the collection, international transfer, storage, and processing of your information.

back to top

#### California Visitors

For additional information for residents of the State of California, click here.

back to top

#### CBS Local Privacy Protections for Children

Most CBS Local Services are intended for a general audience and do not knowingly collect or store contact information about children under the age of 13. Some CBS Local Services may ask for your full date of birth to ensure that they are not collecting information from children under 13 or to identify when additional steps may need to be taken when information has been collected from children under 18. In instances where a CBS Local Service has actual knowledge that it collects information from children, or offers a service directed toward children as defined under applicable laws, it will comply with those laws. To read about our privacy policy for children under the age of 13, please see the CBS Local Children’s Privacy Policy.

back to top

#### User-Generated Content

Some CBS Local Services enable users to submit their own content for use in contests, blogs, over-the-air radio and television broadcasts, online audio and video streams, message boards, and other functions. Publication of user-generated content on the CBS Local Services is subject to our [Terms of Use](http://policies.cbslocal.com/terms-of-use/). Please remember that any information you disclose becomes public information and to exercise caution when choosing to disclose your contact, financial, and other information in a submission. We cannot prevent such information from being used in a manner that may violate this Privacy Policy, the law, or your personal privacy and safety. You should also be aware that we may also engage a third party to provide some of the services associated with the blogs, message boards and similar functions. This third party will collect and host the information that you submit to the CBS Local Services, but will not use any of this information for purposes other than providing the service.

back to top

#### Third Party Websites and Services

Please note that some CBS Local Services may contain links to other websites and services. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of those websites, and we recommend that you review the privacy policies of each website that you visit. When you select a link to a third party website from a CBS Local Service (e.g., if you link to PayPal to pay for a product or service offered by a CBS Local Service), you will be leaving the CBS Local website. Any information that you disclose on the third party website will be governed by that website's privacy policy.

back to top

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and service offerings. If we modify our Privacy Policy, we will update the “Last Modified Date" and such changes will be effective upon posting. If we make any material changes in the way we use your information, we will notify you by email through the email address you most recently provided to us or by posting a prominent notice of the changes on the CBS Local Services.

back to top

#### Questions

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](http://policies.cbslocal.com/privacy/generalinfo.html) and we will endeavor to respond to your request within a reasonable period of time. You may also submit questions or comments using the postal address listed below:

** CBS Local Digital Media  
1700 Broadway, 7th Floor  
New York, NY 10019  
Attn: General Counsel  
**   
We are committed to working with you to obtain a fair resolution of any privacy concern 

back to top

#### Cookies, Web Beacons and Other Similar Technologies

Cookies are small amounts of data that are stored in separate files within your computer's Internet browser. Cookies are accessed and recorded by the websites you visit, and by the companies that show advertisements on these websites, so that they can recognize the same browser.

Web beacons (sometimes called transparent GIFs, clear GIFs, or web bugs) are small strings of code that provide a way for us to deliver a small graphic image (usually invisible) on a web page or in an email. Web beacons can recognize certain types of information on your computer such as cookies, the time and date a page is viewed, and a description of the page where the web beacon is placed. 

**How CBS Local Services Use Cookies, Web Beacons and Other Similar Technologies**  
CBS Local Services use cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies for the following general purposes:

  * To help us recognize your browser as a previous visitor and to save and remember any preferences that may have been set while your browser was visiting one of our Services. For example, if you register on a CBS Local Service, that Service may use a cookie to identify you so that you will not have to log in each time you visit the Service.
  * To help us customize the content and advertisements you are shown while visiting CBS Local Services and potentially other websites. Please read CBS Local Online Advertising  to learn more about our efforts to show you relevant advertising.
  * To help measure and research the effectiveness of our online content, features, advertisements and other communications.
  * CBS Local Services may also allow third parties to place their own cookies within your browser in order to serve you relevant advertising online, to help us measure traffic and effectiveness as described above, to provide you with access to social media networks, functionality and services, and to allow us to conduct surveys and research in which you agree to participate. For instance, [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php), [Google](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/) and [Twitter](https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=en) place their cookies on CBS Local Services to support social network integration and functionality and for use according to their respective privacy policies. For more information, please see the Video Services and Social Networking Policy.
  * Web beacons are used to improve your experience on the CBS Local Services, including helping provide you with content customized to your interests. They also help us understand whether users read email messages and click on links contained in those messages so that we can deliver relevant content and offers. Our web beacons may collect some contact information (e.g., the email address associated with an email that contains a web beacon).
  * CBS Local Services also may include third party web beacons. These web beacons allow third party service providers to collect certain information such as your IP address, your browser type, and the web page that you visited before arriving at and after leaving CBS Local Services. These service providers process the information they collect to audit, research, and report information about the CBS Local Services and advertisements viewed on the CBS Local Services. Third parties that use cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies to help us with traffic measurement, research and analytics include [Adobe Analytics](http://www.adobe.com/marketing-cloud/web-analytics.html), [comScore](http://www.comscore.com/About-comScore/Privacy), [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics), [Nielsen](http://www.nielsen-online.com/corp.jsp?section=leg_prs&nav=1#Optoutchoices), and [ConfirmIT](http://www.confirmit.com/privacy-policy.aspx). Please note that we do not share your contact information with these third parties.

Also, authorized third party service providers may collect non-contact information about your visits to our Services with cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies that may be used to deliver advertisements or marketing tailored to your interests. These third parties may collect information about your online activities over time and across different websites. To opt out of targeted advertisements on third party sites, please see the Managing Third Parties' Behaviorally Targeted Advertising Cookies on Your Computer section of this Privacy Policy.

When you use our search function, your web browser also may send the Internet address, or URL, of the search results page to a third party webpage as part of standard HTTP web protocol. The URL of the search results page may sometimes contain the keywords used in the search query you entered. Some of the advertisements you see may be based on these keywords.

By continuing to use CBS Local Services, you consent to our use of cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies as described above.

To find out more about how you can manage cookies, web beacons and the other similar technologies, see the Managing Cookies section of this Privacy Policy.

**How Third Parties Use Cookies and Other Similar Technologies**

Some of the advertisements you see on CBS Local Services are delivered by third parties who also collect information through cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies about your online activities, either on our Services or across the Internet, so that they may understand your interests and deliver advertisements that are tailored to your interests. These third parties include advertisers, advertising agencies, and ad networks that may collect information when you view or interact with one of their advertisements. To learn more, please read the Third Party Online Advertising section of this Privacy Policy.

In addition, CBS Local works with third parties to help us track the advertisements that are delivered to you to control the number of times you receive the same advertisement, and to analyze the effectiveness of advertising on the CBS Local Services.

Please note that CBS Local does not have access to the information these third parties may collect about your interests to deliver relevant advertising to you. The information practices of these third parties are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Third parties that may serve, track and/or analyze advertisements on our Services, and thereby may collect information about your online activities on such Services include, but are not limited to [AdsWizz](http://www.adswizz.com/), [comScore](https://www.comscore.com/Products/Advertising-Analytics/validated-Media-Essentials), [eXelate](http://exelate.com/), [Google/DFP](http://www.google.com/doubleclick/?hl=bg), [LiveIntent](http://liveintent.com/), [Moat](http://www.moat.com/), [Nielsen](http://www.nielsen.com/us/en/solutions/capabilities/digital-ad-ratings.html) and [Triton Digital](http://www.tritondigital.com/).

To find out more about how you can manage the information collected by these companies, see the Managing Cookies section of this Privacy Policy.

**Do Not Track**

Some Internet browsers include the ability to transmit “Do Not Track" signals. Since uniform standards for “Do Not Track" signals have not been adopted, CBS Local Services do not process or respond to “Do Not Track" signals. To learn more about “Do Not Track", please visit “[All About Do Not Track](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/)".

**Mobile Devices**

Certain mobile devices provide various capabilities that can be used, for example, to identify the physical location of such devices. Mobile devices also transmit Caller ID data when a call is made or text message is sent. CBS Local Services may collect, use, transmit, process and maintain unique identifiers, Caller ID data, location-based data, and other similar information when you use your mobile devices, including to provide the services you request, tell you about offers we think you will value and improve your experience on CBS Local Services. CBS Local Services also may require you to provide your mobile phone number to participate in certain services or features and that number may be associated with such information.

back to top

#### Managing Cookies

Whether cookies are placed on your computer or mobile device is something you can control. This section describes how you can manage the cookies that are placed on your computer or mobile device by CBS Local and third parties.

**Managing Third Parties’ Behaviorally Targeted Advertising Cookies on Your Computer**

A number companies that use cookies to collect information about your online activities using web-based advertising are members of the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) ("NAI"). The NAI offers a single location to opt out of receiving tailored ads from member companies. To opt out of information collection by NAI member companies, or to obtain information about the technologies they use or their own privacy policies, please visit the [NAI consumer opt-out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) page. Also, through the Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA"), several media and marketing associations have developed an industry self-regulatory program to give consumers a better understanding of and greater control over ads that are customized based on their online behavior across different websites. To make choices about interest-based ads from participating third parties, please visit the [DAA consumer opt-out](http://www.aboutads.info/consumers) page.

If you opt out of having your information used to deliver advertisements tailored to your interests, you will continue to see advertisements on our Services, but these advertisements may not be as relevant to you.

**Adjusting Your Browser Settings**

You have the option to set your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, notify you when a cookie is set, and delete cookies periodically (including third party behaviorally targeted advertising cookies). Each browser is different, so please refer to the guide below, which describes how to set the cookie options on a number of different browser types. If your browser is not listed below, please visit [All About Cookies](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/), where you may find more information about your specific browser, or select the "Help" menu in your browser.

Web beacons are generally used in conjunction with cookies, so if your browser is set to reject cookies, or if you delete cookies, web beacons will not be able to track your activity as you navigate between websites.

It is up to you whether to allow us or third parties to send you cookies, but if you block cookies, you may not be able to view or access some or all of a CBS Local Service or other websites.

Below you'll find directions to help you disable cookies in some of the most popular desktop browsers and mobile browsers.

Mozilla Firefox version 3.5 or later

  * In the "Tools" menu, select "Options"
  * Under the "Firefox will:" dropdown, select "Use custom settings for history"
  * Uncheck the "Accept Cookies from Sites" box to block all cookies Or
  * Click the "Exceptions" button to enter specific websites that you wish to allow/disallow to set cookies

Internet Explorer version 6 or later

  * In the "Tools" menu, select "Internet Options"
  * Click the "Privacy" tab
  * Move the "Settings" slider up or down to adjust your cookie acceptance settings (moving the slider all the way to the top will block all cookies) or
  * Click the "Sites" button to enter specific websites that you wish to allow/disallow to set cookies

Google Chrome version 4 or later

  * Click the wrench icon in the top right of your browser window
  * Select "Options"
  * Click the "Under the Hood" tab
  * Click the "Content Settings" button
  * Click the option to "Block sites from setting any data" to block all cookies Or
  * Click the "Exceptions" button to enter specific websites that you wish to allow/disallow to set cookies

Safari version 4 or later

  * Click the geared wheel icon in the top right of your browser window.
  * Select "Preferences"
  * Select the "Security" tab
  * Under "Accept Cookies:", click the "Never" option to block all cookies

**Disabling cookies in popular mobile browsers** :

Mobile Safari

  * From your home screen on your iPhone or iPad, click "Settings"
  * Click on "Safari"
  * Click on "Accept Cookies"
  * Select "Never" to block all cookies

Android for Mobile

  * From within the Android browser, hit the menu key.
  * Select "More"
  * Select "Settings"
  * Uncheck the "Accept Cookies" option to block all cookies

Opera Mini on a Blackberry device

  * From within the Opera Mini browser, press the menu key.
  * Scroll down to access the drop down menu of options
  * Select "Settings"
  * Select "Privacy"
  * Change the "Accept cookies" option to "Off" to block all cookies

**Managing Flash Cookies**  
Flash cookies, also called local shared objects (LSOs), function similarly to standard cookies except that they are often larger and are downloaded to a computer or mobile device by the Adobe Flash Player. In some cases, these Flash cookies can be managed through browser settings. Adobe also provides a means of controlling Flash cookies on its Flash Player: Setting Manager page.

**Managing Cookies on CBS Local Mobile Applications**  
CBS Local may place cookies on your mobile device if you download CBS Local applications (“Apps"). These cookies are used for many of the same purposes identified in the Cookies, Web Beacons and Other Similar Technologies section of this Privacy Policy. You may be provided with an opportunity to reject cookies before downloading a CBS Local App, but by downloading an App, you will be deemed to have consented to the collection of information from your mobile device.

back to top

#### CBS Local Online Advertising

In order to customize your experience on the CBS Local Services, we may use cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies to collect information about the content and advertisements you view on our Services and the websites of our business partners. Based on this and other information we may collect about you as described in the Information Collected section of this Privacy Policy, we try to infer your interests and show content and advertising that is more relevant to you. For example, if you access an article about computers on one CBS Local Service, we may show you a computer-related advertisement on another CBS Local Service based on your apparent interests.

We also may receive information from third parties about you and your activities on other websites for the purpose of serving relevant advertisements to you. For example, if you access an article on a third party website about computers, we may use that information to serve you with a computer-related advertisement on a CBS Local Service.

Please note that we may share information about our users with advertisers so that they can measure the effectiveness of advertisements viewed on the CBS Local Services. For example, we may tell advertisers the number of users who clicked on a particular advertisement. We may also use technology, e.g., [Facebook Custom Audiences](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php) and [Measured Marketing](http://measuredmktg.com/) to deliver advertising to you on other websites based on the email address or other personal information you provided to us or through the use of information we received from third parties. This Privacy Policy does not cover the practices of third parties, including those that may disclose information to CBS Local. 

These online-advertising efforts across CBS Local Services do not result in you seeing more advertisements, just more relevant advertising, and they allow us to provide you with free content and services on CBS Local Services. We hope you value our efforts to show you content and advertising that more closely reflects your interests.

Some of the advertisements you see on CBS Local Services are delivered by third parties. To learn more, please read our overview on third party online advertising.

back to top

#### Third Party Online Advertising

Some of the advertisements you see on the CBS Local Services are delivered by third parties who also collect information through their own cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies about your online activities, either on our Services or across the Internet, in an effort to understand your interests and deliver advertisements that are tailored to your interests. These third parties include advertisers, advertising agencies and ad networks that may collect information about you when you view or interact with one of their advertisements and may collect information about your online activities over time and across different websites.

Third parties that may serve, track and/or analyze ads on our Services, and thereby may collect information on such Services about your online activities for the purpose of delivering tailored ads to you include, but are not limited to, [A9](http://www.a9.com/), [Admob](https://www.google.com/admob/), [Criteo ](http://www.criteo.com/), [Google/DFP](http://www.google.com/doubleclick/?hl=bg), [Jivox ](http://jivox.com/), [LiveRail](http://www.liverail.com/), [Mixpo](http://multiscreen.mixpo.com/), [PointRoll](http://www.pointroll.com/), [Sizmek](http://www.sizmek.com/), [Yieldbot](https://www.yieldbot.com/) and [YieldMo](https://yieldmo.com/). CBS Local does not have access to the information these third parties may collect about your interests to deliver relevant advertising to you, and the information practices of these third parties are not covered by this Privacy Policy. These companies may offer a way for you to choose not to have your information used for advertising purposes. You can find more information by clicking on the company names above and following the links to each company's website.

In addition, some of these companies are members of the [Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI")](http://www.networkadvertising.org/), which offers a single location for consumers to opt out of receiving tailored advertisements from member companies. To learn more and opt out of information collection by NAI member companies, please visit the [NAI Consumer Opt-Out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) page. Also, through the Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA"), several media and marketing associations have developed an industry self-regulatory program to give consumers a better understanding of and greater control over advertisements that are delivered based on their online behavior across different CBS Local Services. CBS Local is committed to complying with the DAA's Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. To learn more and make choices about interest-based advertisements from participating third parties, please visit the [DAA Consumer Opt-Out](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) page. 

In addition, CBS Local works with third parties to help us track the advertisements that are delivered to you; in particular, to control the number of times you receive the same advertisement and to analyze the effectiveness of advertising on the CBS Local Services. Third parties that use cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies to help us with traffic measurement, research and analytics include [Adobe Analytics](http://www.adobe.com/marketing-cloud/web-analytics.html), [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics), [ comScore](http://www.comscore.com/About-comScore/Privacy-Policy), [ ConfirmIT ](http://www.confirmit.com/privacy-policy.aspx), [Moat](http://www.moat.com/pages/privacy) and [Nielsen](http://www.nielsen-online.com/corp.jsp?section=leg_prs&nav=1#Optoutchoices). We do not share your contact information with these third parties. 

If you opt out of having your information used to deliver advertisements tailored to your interests, you will continue to see advertisements on our Services, but these advertisements may not be as relevant to you. 

For more information about relevant advertisements delivered by CBS Local, please read the CBS Local Online Advertising section of this Privacy Policy.

back to top

#### Video Services and Social Networking Policy

Your video content viewing activities may be collected through your use of the CBS Local Services. By viewing our video content, you are consenting to share your video activities with others, including what videos you have watched on the Services. Sharing this information will allow you to take advantage of social networking and other features on the Services.

**Social Networking Services**  
CBS Local has partnered with certain third party social networking companies to offer you their services through certain CBS Local Services. For example, you can use third party social networking services such as [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy), [Google+](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) or [Twitter](https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=en) to share information about your experience on our Services with your friends and followers on those services. These social networking services may be able to collect information about you, including your activities on a CBS Local Service, and they also may notify your friends, both on CBS Local Services and on their services, that you are a CBS Local user or about your use of the CBS Local Services, in accordance with applicable law and their own privacy policies. 

By using your CBS Local Services account with a third party social networking service, you consent to share information about you, including video content that you have watched on CBS Local Services, with your friends and followers on those services. You can limit how third party social networking services share your information by visiting your social networking services’ websites and updating your privacy settings. 

In addition, CBS Local Services may request your permission to a) access and collect information available from your social networking account; and b) post information to your friends on your behalf. When you connect your social networking service with your CBS Local Services account, you authorize CBS Local Services to access certain information about you from your social networking service to provide content and services, including to help us tailor our communications to you and develop rich online content and services across the CBS Local Services. The information CBS Local may access from your social networking services is governed by the privacy policies and settings of those third party services.

**Video Measurement Services**  
Some of the CBS Local Services may use cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies that allow market research companies such as Nielsen or comScore to collect information about you, including video content that you have watched on the CBS Local Services. By watching video content on CBS Local Services, you consent to allow us to share information about you with these video measurement services. For more information about Nielsen, please [click here](http://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy). If you do not wish to participate in Nielsen's digital measurement research on mobile platforms, please [click here](http://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy#choice) to opt out. If you choose to opt out, CBS will not share with Nielsen video content viewing information about you. For more information about comScore, [click here](http://www.comscore.com/). Please note that we do not share contact information with video measurement services.

In addition, third party market research services such as Nielsen may access information about you through your social networking services. You can limit the information that such companies may access by visiting your social networking service and updating your privacy settings. [Click here](https://www.facebook.com/help/211774365532736?sr=1&sid=0U3IgVgLaT89shpT3) to read about Facebook's participation in Nielsen’s measurement services, and [here](http://www.nielsen-online.com/corp.jsp?section=leg_prs&nav=1#Optoutchoices) to learn how to opt out of Nielsen measurement services on web browsers. 

back to top

#### CBS Local FCC Requirements

If you send a written communication (including an email) regarding the programming or operation of a CBS radio or television station, your communication may be placed in the public inspection file of that station or made available via electronic file access at the station. In either case, your communication may be subject to review by members of the general public, as required by Federal Communications Commission ("FCC") regulations. Be advised that we are not responsible for information that may be disclosed if your communication is made available for review by members of the general public in compliance with FCC regulations.

back to top

#### California Visitors

Residents of the State of California may request a list of all third parties to which the CBS Local Services has disclosed certain information during the preceding year for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like such a list, please contact us at <http://policies.cbslocal.com/privacy/generalinfo.html>. If you are a California resident under 18 years of age, and a registered user of any website where this policy is posted, you may request removal of content or information you have publicly posted. Please be aware that such a request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information you posted and there may be circumstances in which the law does not require or allow removal, even if requested.

For all requests, you must put the statement "Your California Privacy Rights" in the subject field of your request and include the name of the CBS Local Service with respect to which you are requesting the information. You must also include your full name, street address, city, state, and zip code. We will not accept requests via telephone, postal mail, or facsimile, and we are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or that do not have complete information.

back to top

#### CBS Local Children’s Privacy Policy

CBS Local Services recognize the need to provide additional privacy protections when children visit the websites on which this CBS Local Children's Privacy Policy is posted. The following guidelines supplement our general  Privacy Policy and follow the rules set by the U.S. Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) and other applicable laws. When we use the term “child" or “children" below, we mean an individual under 13 years of age or an individual under 18 years of age where the collection, use, or disclosure of personal information about such an individual is restricted by applicable law. When we use the term "parent" below, we mean to include legal guardians. 

**Information We Collect**  
Children can enjoy content and features on CBS Local Services without directly providing contact information. However, children who wish to participate in sweepstakes, contests, and certain other special activities may need to provide information such as first name, user name, password, email address, date of birth, city and state of residence, and gender.

In the course of participating in interactive features such as chat rooms and message boards, a child may provide us with additional information about himself or herself, such as the contents of his or her postings. Some information, including information collected through  cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies may be collected automatically. For more information, see the "Information we collect automatically on CBS Local Services" section of our general privacy policy.

If we knowingly collect, use or disclose contact information collected from a child, we will provide you notice and obtain parental consent in accordance with applicable law. 

We do not condition a child's participation in an online activity on the child's providing more contact information than is reasonably necessary to participate in that activity. 

Use of Information 

We use the information we collect consistent with the services requested by the child. For example, we may use information provided by the child to: 

  * Send a newsletter, electronic card, and other communication requested by the child;
  * Enable a child's participation in certain interactive features such as games, contests, message boards, chat rooms, song requests, and online scrolling tickers; and
  * Respond to correspondence sent by the child.

We may also use a parent's contact information to communicate with the parent regarding the child's activities on CBS Local Services. For example, if a child wins a sweepstakes or contest, we may use the parent's contact information to conduct prize fulfillment. 

**Disclosure of Information Collected**  
Information collected from children will be disclosed in the same ways described in the Disclosure of Information Collected section of our general Privacy Policy. Third parties who receive contact information collected by CBS Local have agreed to maintain the confidentiality, security and integrity of that information. Parents have the option not to consent to the disclosure of their child's contact information to third parties. Parents may also consent to CBS Local's collection and use of their child's contact information while refusing to permit the disclosure of that information to third parties. 

**Parents' Choices and Access to Children's Information**   
Parents may review the contact information we have collected from their child, refuse to permit us to collect further contact information from their child, and request that any contact information we have collected be deleted from our records. 

To review, update or delete your child's contact information, please [contact us](http://policies.cbslocal.com/privacy/generalinfo.html). You may also send your request to the postal address listed below. To protect your child's safety, we ask for proof of your identity. We may deny access if we believe there is a question about your identity. 

Please note that certain information cannot be deleted because of other legal obligations, such as FCC requirements. 

**Changes to the CBS Local Children's Privacy Policy**  
We may amend the CBS Local Children's Privacy Policy at any time and will make material changes only in conformance with applicable law. We will provide parents with notice of any material changes in the way we intend to collect, use, and share children's contact information. Accordingly, parents should update their contact information to provide us with current email addresses at all times. 

back to top

#### Contact Us

If you need further assistance, please [contact us](http://policies.cbslocal.com/privacy/generalinfo.html). If you would prefer to submit your questions or comments by postal mail, please send a letter to the following address:

** CBS Local Digital Media  
1700 Broadway, 7th Floor  
New York, NY 10019  
Attn: General Counsel  
**

back to top

#### CBS Local Digital Media Privacy Policy FAQ 

We have updated our Privacy Policy to provide visitors of CBS Local Services with a single, uniform policy consistent with our core Privacy Principles. Here, you will find answers to some common questions about our new Privacy Policy. To review the current Privacy Policy, click here.

Why are you updating your Privacy Policy? As CBS Local expands and the laws protecting individual privacy evolve, we update our Privacy Policy accordingly to ensure that we are adhering to all applicable laws and conform to a consistent set of core Privacy Principles followed by our companies

Have you made any substantively material changes to the Privacy Policy? No, we have not made any substantively material changes to our Privacy Policy.

What are the "core" privacy principles that CBS Local follows? Trust is a cornerstone of our mission at CBS Local. We are committed to gaining and maintaining your trust by following five key principles: transparency, choice, access, security, and accountability. For more information, click here.

Will you share my contact information with third parties? Like other businesses, we share contact information (such as name and email address) with vendors who process credit card transactions, with business partners who co-sponsor CBS Local Services, and when we have consent from our users. For more information, click here.

Can you give me an example when you will share my information with third parties? If you enter a sweepstakes that is jointly sponsored by a third party, we may share your contact information with that third party. Also, if you seek to download a free song from a band or listen to a free stream of a band, we might ask you to consent to have your contact information shared with third parties who may contact you about information concerning that band's appearances. This allows us to offer you valuable content for free.

Does CBS Local allow third parties to collect and use data about me for online advertising? Our advertisers may have relationships with third parties who deliver their advertisements on our Services. While delivering these advertisements, these third parties may collect and use information about your activities on our Services (such as the content you viewed). These companies may offer you a way to choose not to have your information used for advertising purposes. To learn more, click here.

Does CBS Local share contact information with other websites or services owned by CBS Corporation? As CBS Corporation continues to expand its online offerings, we will share information with other websites owned by our parent, CBS Corporation, so that we can inform our users better about products and services in which they may be interested. It is up to you to decide whether you want to hear about special offers from us or from other business units owned by CBS Corporation. You can choose not to receive such marketing emails when you register with us, by updating your preferences, by clicking on the “Unsubscribe" link in any email we send, or by contacting us [localcontactus@cbs.com](mailto:localcontactus@cbs.com?Subject=Unsubscribe).

Do you use my data for advertising on CBS Local Services? Like other websites, we are able to offer free content and services through the revenue we receive from advertising on CBS Local Services. We hope you value the advertising you see on our Services, and we may use some data about you to tailor advertisements to your apparent interests. For example, if you visit the CBS Local Services and read articles about computers, we may serve you with a computer-related advertisement when you visit another CBS Local Service. This advertising does not result in you seeing more advertisements; rather, it just means you’ll see more relevant advertisements. To learn more, click here.

What are the benefits to me of the new Privacy Policy? We hope you will find our Privacy Policy easier to read and understand across all CBS Local Services. We are committed to gaining and maintaining your trust. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please [contact us](http://policies.cbslocal.com/privacy/generalinfo.html).
